## Fatih Furkan USTA

Şişli, İstanbul fatihfurkanusta@outlook.com (544) 551 5509 linkedin.com/in/fathfurkn github.com/fatihfurkanusta trailblazer.me/id/fatihfurkanusta



I have been passionate about software since my univercity years, despite studying in a different department. I am proficient creating projects using Java, C#, Spring Boot, .Net and Javascript Technologies, which I actively showcase on my GitHub profile. I possess a strong understanding of Object-Oriented Programming (OOP), SOLID principles, Design Patterns and other essential concepts, applying them consistently in my projects. As a dedicated researcher and acid learner, I am cofident that I can further enhance my skills by contributing to and learning from your company.

## **Projects**

### Speech Master AI

This project is crafted with Spring Boot, ChatGPT API, Bootstrap and Javascript, designed to enhance your English speaking skills.

#### • Cafe Management System

This project is crafted with Spring Boot, Angular, PostgreSql, HTML and CSS, designed to assist in the management of a cafe.

#### Events Project

This project is crafted with C#, Bootstrap, MsSql, Authorization, designed as a site similar to biletix.com.

#### Patika Clone

This project is crafted with Java, Swing and PostgreSql, designed as a clone of Patika.com on desktop.

### Pizza Order

This project is crafted with Python and Qt Designer, designed for ordering pizza.

## **Certificates**

#### **Backend Web Development Path With Intermediate Java**

Patika.Dev - Online February 2023

### **Intruduction to Python**

Global AI Hub – Online

January 2023

### **Beginner Frontend Web Development Path**

Patika.Dev - Online July 2023

## **Backend Web Development Path With Beginner Java**

Patika.Dev - Online January 2023

## **Skills**

- Java
- C#
- Apex
- Javascript

## Languages

• English – Upper-Intermediate

## **Education**

### **Bachelor of Biomedical Engineering**

Pamukkale Univercity - Denizli

September 2015 – September 2020

# **Work Experience**

#### **Biomedical Engineer**

MTS Medikal – İstanbul September 2019 - January 2020

I took an active role in the technical service, installation and sales of Ultrasound Devices and Laser devices. I took part in solving many hardware and software problems.

#### **Intern Engineer**

Renova Medikal Mühendislik – İstanbul September 2019 - January 2020

I have gained hardware and software knowledge about MRI and CT devices. I had the opportunity to put my knowledge into practice. I took part in many malfunctions and solutions of MR and CT devices.

## **Military Service**

### **Rank: Lieutenant**

April 2021 - April 2022